<?xml version="1.0"?>

<config_bld>

<comment>
This is a configuration file for building GAMIL.  It is the file format
produced by the configure script to store a build configuration.  It
may also be read by the configure script (via setting the -defaults
option) to provide a default build configuration.

This file may be edited by hand to quickly customize a configuration.  If
hand editing is done it should be recognized that XML parser used to read
this file is not able to check the file for valid syntax.  Also, the
current parser places some restrictions on the normally valid XML syntax:
1. Attribute values must be enclosed in DOUBLE QUOTED STRINGS!!!
</comment>

<comment>
gamil_bld    GAMIL build directory, contains .o and .mod files
gamil_exedir Directory where GAMIL executable will be created
gamil_root   Root directory of GAMIL distribution
esmf_bld   Build directory for ESMF, only needed if ESMF lib will be built
esmf_root  Root directory of ESMF distribution, only needed if ESMF lib will be built
usr_src    User source directories to prepend to the filepath.  Multiple directories
           are specified as a comma separated list with no embedded white space.
</comment>

<directories
gamil_bld="."
gamil_exedir="."
gamil_root=""
esmf_bld="./esmf"
esmf_root=""
usr_src=""
/>

<comment>
cpl    Is flux coupler used?  0 => no, 1 => yes
dyn    Dynamics package: eul, sld, or fv
phys   Physics package: cam1 or ccm366
lnd    Land model: clm2 or lsm.  Currently this value depends on the
       phys value as follows:  cam1 => clm2, ccm366 => lsm.
ocn    Use SST data or slab ocean model: dom or som
sice   Sea ice package: csim4 or ccmice
pergro Use modifications that allow perturbation growth testing
           0 => no, 1 => yes
</comment>

<packages
cpl="0"
dyn="eul"
phys="cam1"
lnd="clm2"
ocn="dom"
sice="csim4"
pergro="0"
/>

<comment>
res   Horizontal resolution specifier.  The recognized values depend on
      the dynamics type and are contained in the resolution_parameters.xml file.
nlon  Number of longitude grid points
nlat  Number of latitude grid points
nlev  Number of vertical levels
nadv  Number of advected constituents
nnadv Number of non-advected constituents
trm   Maximum Fourier wavenumber
trn   Highest degree of the Legendre polynomials for m=0
trk   Highest degree of the associated Legendre polynomials
pcols Maximum number of columns in a chunk
</comment>

<resolution
res="60x128"
nlon=""
nlat=""
nlev="26"
nadv="1"
nnadv="4"
trm=""
trn=""
trk=""
pcols="16"
/>

<comment>
gamil_exe    Name of GAMIL executable
cc         User specified C compiler overrides Makefile default (linux only).
fc         User specified Fortran compiler overrides Makefile default.
debug      Switch to enable debugging options for Fortran compiler.
fflags     User specified Fortran compiler options to append to Makefile defaults.
spmd       Switch to enable or disable building SPMD version of GAMIL.
smp        Switch to enable or disable building SMP version of GAMIL.
nc_inc     Directory containing NetCDF include files.
nc_lib     Directory containing NetCDF library.
mpi_inc    Directory containing MPI include files.
mpi_lib    Directory containing MPI library.
</comment>

<makefile
gamil_exe="gamil"
cc=""
fc=""
debug="0"
fflags=""
spmd=""
smp=""
nc_inc=""
nc_lib=""
mpi_inc=""
mpi_lib=""
/>

</config_bld>
